<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ModernApps Skills 101 – ModernApps Skills 101</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/</link><description>Recent content on ModernApps Skills 101</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Docs: Course Introduction</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/courseintroduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/courseintroduction/</guid><description>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#about-this-course">About this Course&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#prerequisites">Prerequisites&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#course-input--feedback">Course Input &amp;amp; Feedback&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#content-accuracy-and-refresh-cycle">Content Accuracy and Refresh Cycle&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#thank-you-for-participating">Thank you for participating!&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="important-notice">Important Notice:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>The Enrollment, testing and digital badge features will be removed on Friday February 18th, 2022. Please ensure you have completed any test and digital badge requests prior to this date. The course materials will still be available.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="about-this-course">About this Course&lt;/h2>
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5ScnewvBayk" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div>
&lt;p>This course provides an introduction to the ModernApps Learning community. The community is much more than just content and is really intended to be an active community of professionals learning and working towards applying new skills in cloud native technologies.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The ModernApps Learning community uses devops tools to deliver all the features provided by the platform to participate in courses, collaboration and other community assets. When you register with the community you fill out an issue ticket. To enroll in a course you will post a new file to the course repository. When you take a test you will modify an existing file in the repository. While registration, enrollment and testing are normal features of Learning Management Systems (LMS), the ModernApps Learning Platform is not an LMS, it is a devops system where each of these features is implemented as a CI/CD workflow using GitHub Actions. This means participating in a course is just like working on a devops project; you will use GitHub messaging to collaborate with peers and open pull requests to edit or post files to a repository to participate in each course.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>By the time you have taken your first course, you will have learned these core skills which represent the most common and important skills to begin participating and contributing to a modern devops and/or open source projects.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>While participating in a course gets you started on foundational devops skills, the ModernApps Learning Platform provides a unique opportunity for members to learn and practice devops skills in a real production context. Every aspect of the ModernApps Learning Program is managed openly in conjunction with the community. Our vision, goals, roadmap, planning, code, infrastructure etcetera are all managed by and for the community, which is designed with guidelines and guardrails to help participants learn by doing in a step-by-step guided path towards increasing production-grade experience.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In this course you will learn the foundational skills to participate in ModernApps Learning courses at the 100 level, including how to register with the community, use community collaboration tools, participate in events, enroll in courses, take tests, and request course completion badges.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you complete all steps in this course, you can request a certificate of completion by following the instructions provided at the end of the course.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This course is a community effort, to be able to keep up the material, we really need your help to report issues, suggest improvements, or help with the many volunteer opportunities available to support the community.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="prerequisites">Prerequisites&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This course has no prerequisites.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="course-input--feedback">Course Input &amp;amp; Feedback&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Your feedback for this course is critical to help ensure we can improve course content and quality and is greatly appreciated!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you see any problems or suggestions for improvement in this course, the community is very grateful for your help. The simplest way to provide your input is to click the Edit this page link on the right nav bar on each page on this site, and it will open a page to a simple web text editor where you can easily make any update or suggested input you have and then click a button to submit your update. If the course administrators approve your update, the commit and each line you update will be shown on your public Github profile and add value to your professional portfolio, and you will be listed as a contributor to the site.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you would prefer to provide feedback through a feedback form, all feedback is crucial to helping the community provide the best content we can. To submit feedback, general questions or support requests, please click the “Open Issue Ticket” link found on the right navigation bar on each page of this course site.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The community thanks you for your feedback and contributions!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="content-accuracy-and-refresh-cycle">Content Accuracy and Refresh Cycle&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We make a strong effort to keep the content in this course as current as possible, however the Tanzu Portfolio is rapidly growing and there may be times where this course may not include the newest updates. Always refer to the official VMware Tanzu Portfiolio Website and your VMware account team for the latest details on products covered in this course.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As part of our effort to keep this course as up-to-date as possible, this course is on a continuous update lifecycle. This means that the course can be updated at any time, and new content and requirements may be added while you are taking your course. We will make effort to notify members in advance of any significant updates are made to minimize any unexpected changes to course completion requirements.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="thank-you-for-participating">Thank you for participating!&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Docs: Content Overview</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/contentoverview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/contentoverview/</guid><description>
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/k5WIDlV_FBo" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Docs: Collaboration, Feedback, and Support</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/collaborationfeedbacksupport/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/collaborationfeedbacksupport/</guid><description>
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Aviobz_z7hE" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Docs: Community Membership</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/communitymembership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/communitymembership/</guid><description>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#video-overview">Video Overview&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#about-community-membership">About Community Membership&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#how-to-register">How to Register&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#link-to-membership-registration-form">Link to Membership Registration Form&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="video-overview">Video Overview&lt;/h3>
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CIRecX6M9Go" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div>
&lt;h3 id="about-community-membership">About Community Membership&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The Free ModernApps Learning Community Membership unlocks access to many key community assets including:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Membership in the ModernAppsNinja Github Organization and Members Github Team&lt;/li>
&lt;li>ModernApps Learning Mailer list emails about community events and key content updates&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Ability to take course tests and request certificates of completion&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Member Repository and Github Pages site to display Member Course Records, Completion Certificates and Achievements&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Access to member discussion boards&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Access to submit blogs, courses and course contents, access course template and other community resources for contributors&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Course Enrollment and particpation reflects github commits on Members github profile and listed as contributor on ModernAppsNinja Github Org&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Access to participatory gitops/devops learning events, hackathons and exercises where members can gain organizational permissions including collaborator and maintainer achievements&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Please Note: We are currently making some changes to our backend course hosting, and some courses may require additional registration steps until we complete this transition. If a course requires any additional registration steps, instructions will be provided in the course materials.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="how-to-register">How to Register&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Note: You must have a Github account and be logged in to github to register. Regardless of what values you type into the form, the github account you are logged in as at the time you submit the registration form will be used, so please be sure you are logged in to github with the account you want to register with.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We use gitops/devops tools for participatory actions in the program to help ensure participants are comfortable with these important new skills.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To register you will fill out a simple form in a github issue ticket. Its important that you fill out the form as instructed, and not modify the form spacing or punctuation as that could interfere with the automated workflows that process your registration.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here is an example registration form:&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;pre tabindex="0" style="background-color:#f8f8f8;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4">&lt;code class="language-bash" data-lang="bash">preferredEmailAddress: &lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&lt;/span>
firstName: &lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&lt;/span>
lastName: &lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&lt;/span>
twitterUsername: &lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&lt;/span>
linkedinUsername: &lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&lt;/span>
isVmwareEmployee: &lt;span style="color:#204a87">false&lt;/span>
vmwareEmailAddress: &lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&lt;/span>
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/div>&lt;p>As you can see in the form above, each field has an empty pair of quotation marks where you can fill in your registration data. For example if your first name is John, you would enter &lt;code>firstName: &amp;quot;John&amp;quot;&lt;/code> only adding your name between the quotation marks, without changing the line in any other way.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Please note that First and Last Name fields do not infer which is the family name, it infers the display order. For example if you enter first name as &lt;code>Juan&lt;/code> and your last name as &lt;code>Dew&lt;/code>, your member repository homepage would say &lt;code>Welcome to the ModernApps Learning Member Page for Juan Dew&lt;/code>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You may notice the &lt;code>isVmwareEmployee: false&lt;/code> line does not have quotation marks around the value &lt;code>false&lt;/code> - because it is a boolean value, it does not require quotations. If you are a vmware employee, please change this value to &lt;code>isVmwareEmployee: true&lt;/code>; otherwise leave the value as false and do not change this line.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Required Values:&lt;/strong> &lt;code>preferredEmailAddress&lt;/code>, &lt;code>firstName&lt;/code>, &lt;code>lastName&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Optional Values:&lt;/strong> &lt;code>twitterUsername&lt;/code>, &lt;code>linkedinUsername&lt;/code>, &lt;code>vmwareEmailAddress&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here is an example registration form filled in with fake user values:&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;pre tabindex="0" style="background-color:#f8f8f8;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4">&lt;code class="language-bash" data-lang="bash">preferredEmailAddress: &lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;janedoe@fakeaddress.com&amp;#34;&lt;/span>
firstName: &lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;Jane&amp;#34;&lt;/span>
lastName: &lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;Doe&amp;#34;&lt;/span>
twitterUsername: &lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;janedoe&amp;#34;&lt;/span>
linkedinUsername: &lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;janedoe&amp;#34;&lt;/span>
isVmwareEmployee: &lt;span style="color:#204a87">false&lt;/span>
vmwareEmailAddress: &lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&lt;/span>
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/div>&lt;p>After you have completed filling in the registration form, click the &lt;code>Submit new issue&lt;/code> button and an automated workflow will commence that will trigger github to send an email invitation to join the ModernAppsNinja github org. This email will be sent from github to the email account associated with the registrants' github acount.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You must accept the email invitation from GitHub to join the ModernAppsNinja github org.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After you accept the Github invitation and join the organization, an automated workflow will commence that will build your member repository and github pages site. Once your site is ready, the workflow will post a message with the details of your new site on github mentioning you, which will trigger github to send you a notification to the email address associated with your github account. Your new member page will initially be blank, however as you register for courses and earn achievements, they will be posted to your member page.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Please note that we are currently transitioning courses to a new backend system and some courses are still on the old system. Course records from the old system may not be immediately reflected on the member page, but we will ensure that all records from our previous system get transferred and reflected on your member page soon.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="link-to-membership-registration-form">Link to Membership Registration Form&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Before submitting your registration please note that ModernApps Learning is hosted on public Github Repositories, and the records of processing this information can be publicly accessed. All records of participation are reflected on our public github sites and repositories and may be visible to other members or the general public. Participation in ModernApps Learning does not require you to submit confidential information, and asks that you do not submit any information you desire to be kept secret, as all information and particiapation data on this site should be considered public information.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>&lt;a href="https://github.com/ModernAppsNinja/modernappsninja.github.io/issues/new?assignees=modernappsninjabot&amp;amp;labels=newuserregistration&amp;amp;template=joinrequest.md&amp;amp;title=Request+to+Join+ModernApps+Ninja+Github+Org">Please click here to access the Membership Registration Form&lt;/a>&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;hr></description></item><item><title>Docs: Course Enrollment</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/courseenrollment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/courseenrollment/</guid><description>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#video-overview">Video Overview&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#enroll-for-this-course">Enroll for this course&lt;/a>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#step-1---open-the-new-course-enrollment-document-link">Step 1 - Open the new course enrollment document link&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#step-2---name-your-file">Step 2 - Name your file&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#step-3---add-a-line-to-your-file">Step 3 - Add a line to your file&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#step-4---submit-your-enrollment-document">Step 4 - Submit your enrollment document&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="important-notice">Important Notice:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>The Enrollment, testing and digital badge features will be removed on Friday February 18th, 2022. Please ensure you have completed any test and digital badge requests prior to this date. The course materials will still be available.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="video-overview">Video Overview&lt;/h3>
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZwomDsloyHg" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div>
&lt;h3 id="enroll-for-this-course">Enroll for this course&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>You must first be a member of the community before you can enroll for this course. Ensure that you have fully completed the community member enrollment process before proceeding.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To enroll for this course, follow the detailed instructions below to post a simple file with your github username to this repository. This process, while simple to follow, helps participants to gain experience and comfort, and validate their knowledge with foundational devops tools and process.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Posting a file to enroll uses the git pull request process, which is one of the most important and common foundational skills for participating in devops, cloud native, and infrastructure modernization initiatives.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This process will also show on your public github profile that you have made a commit, the course also provides several additional exercises throughout where you will make commits to gain additional git experience while enhancing your github and professional profiles.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="step-1---open-the-new-course-enrollment-document-link">Step 1 - Open the new course enrollment document link&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>The Course Enrollment Process Requires that you have a github account, and that you are signed in using the github account you want to be enrolled for the course. If you attempt to enroll a different account than the account you are signed in as, the process will fail.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Please right click the following link and select the option to open it in a new browser tab, so you can keep this instruction page open in the current tab to guide you through the process.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://github.com/ModernAppsNinja/modernappsskills101_ms4043/tree/main/static/admin/userdata/registered_members">Right Click Here and select the option to open link in new tab&lt;/a> and click on &lt;code>Add File &amp;gt; Create new file&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="step-2---name-your-file">Step 2 - Name your file&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Note the page displays a message that &lt;code>You’re making changes in a project you don’t have write access to. Submitting a change will write it to a new branch in your fork YOUR_GITHUB_USERNAME/COURSE_REPOSITORY_NAME, so you can send a pull request.&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The pull request process works by submitting a copy of your new or updated file to the repository, which will only be applied to the course repository if a course administrator approves the request. Because you do not have write access to the repository, github will create a special copy called a &lt;code>fork&lt;/code> of the course repository within your github account with your new or updated files, and use your copy to save the updates you&amp;rsquo;re submitting to the official course repository as shown in the following steps.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In your browser tab to the new enrollment document, above the document editor in the file name field, type in the name of the file in the format &lt;code>your_github_username.yml&lt;/code>, replacing the value &lt;strong>your_github_username&lt;/strong> with the username for your github account.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The following screenshot shows an example of this step using the github username &lt;code>Oni-no-Hanzo&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Note:&lt;/strong> If needed, you can verify your github username by clicking on your github profile menu, which can be found on the upper right hand corner on any github page if you are signed in.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://modernapps.ninja/course_repo_template_ct8279/admin/assets/images/course_registration_file_naming.png" alt="Screenshot of File Naming">&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="step-3---add-a-line-to-your-file">Step 3 - Add a line to your file&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>On line 1 in the document editor, type &lt;code>status: in-progress&lt;/code> as shown in the following screenshot:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://modernapps.ninja/course_repo_template_ct8279/admin/assets/images/course_registration_file_editing.png" alt="Screenshot of File Editing">&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="step-4---submit-your-enrollment-document">Step 4 - Submit your enrollment document&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Scroll to the bottom of the enrollment document page and click &lt;code>Propose New File&lt;/code> as shown in the following image:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://github.com/ModernAppsNinja/course_repo_template_ct8279/blob/main/static/admin/assets/images/propose_changes.png" alt="Propose New File Screenshot">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After you click &lt;code>Propose New File&lt;/code>, your browser will be redirected to the &lt;code>Comparing Changes&lt;/code> page with all the configuration all setup so all you sould need to do is click &lt;code>Create Pull Request&lt;/code> &amp;mdash; but before you click, please review the other details shown on the comparing changes and observe that the file you created and the lines added are shown, so you can easily review and verify your proposed changes before submitting.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After you click &lt;code>Create pull request&lt;/code>, an automated GitHub Action worklow will initiate that will do the following actions:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>verify that your github account is a member of the modernappsninja organization&lt;/li>
&lt;li>verify the filename of the submitted document matches the github username of the logged-in user that submitted the pull request&lt;/li>
&lt;li>if the above items are successfully validated:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>add the course record page to the members profile repository to display course progress and completion records&lt;/li>
&lt;li>add a message to the pull request ticket with the URL for the members course record page&lt;/li>
&lt;li>trigger github to send an email from github to the email address for the github user account that submitted the pull request including the message from the previous step&lt;/li>
&lt;li>approve and merge the new document you submitted into the registered members directory for this course&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>This completes the course enrollment process, once you have completed the above steps, you can proceed through the course and participate in any steps such as tests and completion certificates that require course enrollment.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thank you!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Docs: Taking Tests</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/takingtests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/takingtests/</guid><description>
&lt;p>All Modernapps Learning content is publicly accessible and available openly, however a free membership is required to take tests and recieve a certificate of completion for the course. You must first &lt;a href="https://modernapps.ninja/about/membership/">join the community&lt;/a> and register for this course per the instructions in the course introduction section before attempting to submit a test.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ModernApps Learning tests use devops tools and processes so the testing system itself provides both experience with and validation of foundational devops skills.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#instructions">Instructions&lt;/a>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#additional-test-instruction-reference">Additional Test Instruction Reference&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#test-answer-response-sheet">Test Answer Response Sheet&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#test-1-questions">Test 1 Questions&lt;/a>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#this-concludes-test-1-please-use-the-navigation-bar-to-proceed-to-the-next-page">This concludes Test 1. Please use the navigation bar to proceed to the next page.&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MmZ459hoq3k" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div>
&lt;h2 id="instructions">Instructions&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This test uses automated grading, you must follow the instructions exactly to ensure automated grading will complete successfully.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To complete the test you must review the questions on this page, and fill in your answers on a seperate answer sheet provided below. We recommend opening the answer sheet for the test in a seperate browser tab so you can fill in the answers as you proceed through the questions.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Every question in this test is titled &amp;ldquo;Question&amp;rdquo; followed by its order, for example Question1, Question2 etc&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>All questions will provide a list of possible answers. Each possible answer is represented by a lowercase letter, the first response is option &amp;ldquo;a&amp;rdquo;, the second is option &amp;ldquo;b&amp;rdquo; and so on, as shown in the example questions below.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Answer sheet will open in Github&amp;rsquo;s web-based editor, similar to the image shown below:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://modernapps.ninja/vspheretanzu101_vt7301/admin/assets/images/blank_test_screen_example.png" alt="Example Test Response Sheet">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After you fill in your answer sheet, you will submit your responses as a git &lt;a href="https://docs.github.com/en/github/collaborating-with-issues-and-pull-requests/about-pull-requests">pull request&lt;/a> following the instructions provided below, which will trigger a workflow that will grade your responses and provide your test grading sheet.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="additional-test-instruction-reference">Additional Test Instruction Reference&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>If you would like to see additional examples or more thorough instructions, please see &lt;a href="https://modernapps.ninja/course_repo_template_ct8279/docs/reference/testinstructions/">How to Take a Test Instructions&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It is important that you follow the instructions carefully to ensure the automated grading process completes successfully.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="test-answer-response-sheet">Test Answer Response Sheet&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Please right click the following link to the test answer response sheet and select to open it in a new tab. The questions for this test will be provided below in this page, but you will need to enter your responses in the answer response sheet.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://github.com/modernappsninja/modernappsskills101_ms4043/edit/main/static/admin/userdata/tests/test1.yml">test1 Answer Response Sheet&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="test-1-questions">Test 1 Questions&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="question1-did-you-register-with-the-modernapps-learning-community----omit-in-toc---">&lt;strong>Question1:&lt;/strong> Did you register with the ModernApps Learning Community? &lt;!-- omit in toc -->&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Please enter &lt;code>a&lt;/code> for yes and &lt;code>b&lt;/code> for no&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;pre tabindex="0" style="background-color:#f8f8f8;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4">&lt;code class="language-yml" data-lang="yml">&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">Answers&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">a&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">Yes&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">b&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">No&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/div>&lt;h4 id="question2-did-you-enroll-in-this-course----omit-in-toc---">&lt;strong>Question2:&lt;/strong> Did you enroll in this course? &lt;!-- omit in toc -->&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Please select the best response:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;pre tabindex="0" style="background-color:#f8f8f8;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4">&lt;code class="language-yml" data-lang="yml">&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">Answers&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">a&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">No&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">b&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000">Tomato&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">c&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">Yes&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">d&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000">Maybe&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/div>&lt;h4 id="question3-which-of-the-following-are-fruits---omit-in-toc---">&lt;strong>Question3:&lt;/strong> Which of the following are fruits?&lt;!-- omit in toc -->&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Select the best 3 responses:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;pre tabindex="0" style="background-color:#f8f8f8;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4">&lt;code class="language-yml" data-lang="yml">&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">Answers&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">a&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000">Turtle&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">b&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000">Banana&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">c&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000">Dog&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">d&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000">Apple&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">e&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000">Cat&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#204a87;font-weight:bold">f&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000;font-weight:bold">:&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline"> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#000">Peach&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#f8f8f8;text-decoration:underline">
&lt;/span>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/div>&lt;h5 id="this-concludes-test-1-please-use-the-navigation-bar-to-proceed-to-the-next-page">This concludes Test 1. Please use the navigation bar to proceed to the next page.&lt;/h5></description></item><item><title>Docs: Learn By Doing</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/learnbydoing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/learnbydoing/</guid><description>
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yDVqt9jz9Pw" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Docs: Course Completion and Badge</title><link>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/coursecompletion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 18:34:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://modernappsninja.github.io/modernappsskills101_ms4043/docs/coursecompletion/</guid><description>
&lt;p>If you have completed all tests in the course and received over 70% correct responses, you can make an automated request to recieve a certificate of completion for this course.&lt;/p>
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_XgvpPML0FQ" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div>
&lt;p>To request for your certificate of completion:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>In a new tab navigate to: &lt;a href="https://github.com/ModernAppsNinja/modernappsskills101_ms4043/tree/main/static/admin/userdata/certs_awarded">https://github.com/ModernAppsNinja/modernappsskills101_ms4043/tree/main/static/admin/userdata/certs_awarded&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Click on the &lt;code>Add file&lt;/code> button to add a new file&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Name the file using your own github username in the format &lt;code>yourgithubusername.yml&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In the body of the file type: &lt;code>Status: Completed&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Click on &lt;code>Propose new file&lt;/code> and then &lt;code>Create pull request&lt;/code> to submit your new file.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>When you have submitted your new file as per described in the steps above (also called making a pull request) it will trigger an automated github action workflow that will:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Compare the total quantity of tests in the course with the quantity of tests you have completed to ensure you have completed all required tests for the course&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Tabulate the total quantity of all test questions from all tests&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Compare the quantity of questions you have answered correctly against the total quantity of questions for all tests to ensure you have attained a minimum of 70% correct answers&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Post grade report and updated course record card to your member repository&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Append a message to the pull request to notify the requesting user the course grading is complete, the result, and links to the updated grade report and course record card.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The requesting members github account will be mentioned in the posted message, which will trigger a github notification to the requestors github account and associated email address.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>In the event that a user requests a certificate and does not have the minimum required grade to pass, a grade report will be provided that will include details on the percent of correct answers for each test in the course, highlighting which test(s) may need to be retaken to achieve a passing grade. Members can then retake any tests necesarry to increase their grade, and then repeat the above process again to request that the certificate service run again.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you encounter any problems with testing or with the certificate process, please open an issue ticket on this course.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>